Guide to the Ramón Hernández Tejano Music Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Artist Files, 1922-2019, undated
  - Male Artist Files
    - Tony De La Rosa - Audiovisual material, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - José Rubén De León, 2017 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Mike De Léon, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Nabor De Leon, 2012, 2018, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - De Los Muertos, 2009, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Toby De Luna, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Arthur Dee and the Be-Boppers, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Johnny Degollado, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Johnny Degollado - Clippings, 1990, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Del Castillo, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Del Castillo - Clippings, 2001-2014, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Dan Del Santo, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Juan Manuel Delgado, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Porfirio Delgado, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Dan Del Santo, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Juan Manuel Delgado, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - The Dell Kings, 1962-[1965], undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - The Dell Kings, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - The Dell Kings - Clippings, 2006, 2013, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - The Dell-Tones, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Los Desperadoz - Photographs, 2001, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Los Desperadoz - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Los Desperadoz - Negatives and slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Los Desperadoz - Concert and event publicity, 1990-2013, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Los Desperadoz, 1991, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Los Desperadoz - Album covers, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Los Desperadoz - Ramón Hernández material, 1990, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Los Desperadoz - Clippings, 1988-2016, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Los Desperadoz - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Los Desperadoz - Promotional material, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Destino, 1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Desveladoz, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - La Devocion de Danny Perez, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Dezeo, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - La Dezz, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Dezzeo, 1994, 2015, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz - Photographs, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz - Lyrics, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz - Production designs, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz - Publicity, 1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz - Ramón Hernández material, 1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz - Clippings, 1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz - Magazines, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz: Promotional material, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Alejandro Diaz, Jr., undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Emilio "El Charro" Diaz, 2014-2015, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Emilio "El Charro" Diaz - Clippings, 2015, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Jerry Diaz, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Juan Diaz, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Lucky Diaz, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Michael Diaz, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Steve Diaz y La Senzacion!, 1993, 1995, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Didier, 1988-1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - La Diferencia, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - La Diferenzia - Photographs, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - La Diferenzia - Publicity, 1994-2009, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - La Diferenzia - Albums, 1994-2009 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - La Diferenzia - Clippings, 1994-2015, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - La Diferenzia - Magazines, 1995-1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Los Dinnos-Aurios, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Los Dinos, 2006, 2009, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - La Distancia, 2008, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Divino, 1992, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Division del Norte, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - DJ Alfredo, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - DJ Kane, 2004, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - DJ Kane - Clippings, 2004-2017, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - DJ Mike, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Dogman and the Shepherds, 1986, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Jay Dominguez and the Stoney Ridge Band, 1986, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Jay Dominguez and the Stoney Ridge Band - Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Los Dominantes del Norte, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Domingo Live, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Manuel "Cowboy" Donley, 1988, 2011, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Los Donneños, 1988, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Los Dos Amigos, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Los Dos Gilbertos - Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Los Dos Gilbertos - Publicity, 1989-2013, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Los Dos Gilbertos - Ramón Hernández material, 1986-1990, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Los Dos Gilbertos - Clippings, 1986-1999, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Los Dos Gilbertos - Promotional material, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Downtown Elvis, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Los Dudes - Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Los Dudes - Sheet music, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Los Dudes - Ramón Hernández material, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Los Dudes - Clippings, 1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Duelo, 2009-2011 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - El Dueto Carta Blanca, 2008-2010, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Jesse y Beto Duran y Los Aguilillas, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Fred Dutchover, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - DVA Kidz, 2014, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - DVA Kidz - Audiovisual material, 2013, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Dyamante, 2001, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Los Dynamos, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Dynasty, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Jimmy Edward - Photographs, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Jimmy Edward - Personal, 2003, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Jimmy Edward - Concert and event publicity, 2009-2017, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Jimmy Edward - Album covers, 1988, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Jimmy Edward - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-1986, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Jimmy Edward - Clippings, 1976-2015, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - El Dorado, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - El Paso, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - The Electric Cowboys, 2006, 2017 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Chano Elizondo, 1997, 2012, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Johnny Elizondo, 1995, 2000, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Los Enmascarados, 2006, 2009, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Arthur Rojas Emerson, 1994, 1996, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Abraham "Abie" Epstein, 2012, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - The Eptones, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - David Escalante, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Joe Escalante, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Escalofrio, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Gilbert Escamilla, 1990, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Mario Escamilla, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Escandalo, 2000, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Eligio Escobar - Photographs, 1966, 1973, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Eligio Escobar - Artist biographies and clippings, 2002, 2008, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Eligio Escobar - Concert and event publicity, 1987-1999, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Eligio Escobar - Ramón Hernández material, 1996, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Cleto Escobedo, Jr. - Photographs, 1961-2006, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Cleto Escobedo, Jr. - Personal, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Cleto Escobedo, Jr. - Jimmy Kimmel Show, 2013, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Cleto Escobedo, Jr. - Ramón Hernández material, 2006-2014, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Cleto Escobedo, Jr. - Clippings, 2007-2013, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Gilbert Escobedo, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Ralph Escobedo, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Roy Escobedo, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - The Escorts, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Eskándal, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - E.S.P., undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Ramon R. Esparza, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Esperanza - Photographs, 1999, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Esperanza - Publicity, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Esperanza - Ramón Hernández material, 1999, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Esperanza - Audiovisual material, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Jeromy Espinosa, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Espiritu Norteño, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Albert Esquivel, 1995, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Albert Esquivel - Clippings, 1995-2007, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Carrie Esquivel, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Danny Esquivel, 2012, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Jon Esquivel, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Estéfan, 1995, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Estéfan - Concert and event publicity, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Estéfan - Clippings, 1995-1996, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Estéfan - Audiovisual material, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Estilo, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Nacho Estrada, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Estrella, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Estrella - Magazines, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Estrella del Norte, 1988-1991, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Estrella del Norte - Clippings, 1988-1992, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Los Estrenos de Mando Garza, 1985, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Estruendo, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Eterno, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Eterno - Audiovisual material, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Európa, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Jon Everett, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Expedition, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - La Experiencia, 2003, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Los Exitos, 2018, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Expressions, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Extreme Heat, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Eye 2 Eye, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - El Eztilo, 2014, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Raúl Fabre, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - La Fabrica, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Los Fabulosos Cuatro, 1981, 2002, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Los Fabulosos Cuatro - Juan Jose and Michael Hinojosa's deaths, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Los Fabulosos Cuatro - Audiovisual material, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Faith, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Noé Falcón - Fabulus Falcons, 1986, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fallout, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fama - Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Fama - Publicity, 1995-2001, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Fama - Clippings, 1989-2001, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Fame, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - La Familia Fama, 1988, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Family Style Tejano Band, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Fandango USA - Photographs, 1991, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Fandango USA, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Fandango USA - Ramón Hernández materials, 1987-1988, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Fandango USA - Clippings, 1988-1993, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Fantasia, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Los Fantasmas del Valle, 2008, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - David Farias, 2015, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Jody Farias, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - La Farra, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Jesse Favela, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Tony Faz, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Los Federales, 2016 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Fenix, 1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - La Feria, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Mario Fernandez, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - La Fiebre - Publicity photographs, 1988, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - La Fiebre - Concert and event publicity, 1990, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - La Fiebre - Album covers, 1991, 1993, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - La Fiebre - Publicity, 1997, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - La Fiebre - Ramón Hernández material, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - La Fiebre - Clippings, 1993-1997, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - La Fiebre - Audiovisual material, 2017, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Fiel, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Fiesta Noche Del Rio Dancers, 1983-1993, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Isaac Figueroa, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Lupe Figueroa, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Final Cut, 2012, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Frankie Firme, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - First Light, 1983-2013, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Los Fiscales, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - The Five Angels, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Five Star, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Five Voices, 2016 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Flippers, 2016 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Alexis Flores, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Amadeo Flores, 1995, 2012, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Angel Flores, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Jaime Flores, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Raphael Flores, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Sonny Flores, 2010, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Sonny Flores - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Los Folkloristas, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Fonseca, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Manny Fonseca, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - The Force, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - La Formula, 1986, 2013, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Johnny Francis, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Frankie Jr. y Grupo Caballero, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - La Franz, 1985, 2001, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Frecuenzia Sol, 2015, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Freedom Express de Danny Martinez, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Fresco Fury, 1995-1996, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Frijoles Romanticos, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Los Fronterizos de CD Acuna, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Jerry Fuentes Jr., undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Joe Fuentes y La Union, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Rick Fuentes and the Brown Express, 2017-2018, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - La Fuerza, 1994-2006, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Mike G. y Los 4 Realez, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Concert tickets and backstage passes, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Publicity, 1999, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Ramón Hernández material, 1990, 1997, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Clippings, 1990-2014, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Audiovisual material, 2014, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Oscar G. y Grupo Sol - Promotional material, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Ricky G., 2008, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Nick Gaitán, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Los Galanes, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Joe Gallardo, 2005, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Bob Gallarza - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Bob Gallarza - Publicity, 2001, 2007, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Bob Gallarza - Ramón Hernández material, 1990, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Bob Gallarza - Clippings, 1191-2009, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Los Gallegos, 2006, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Los Gallitos del Valle, 2001, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Los Gallos de Paris, 2001, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Los Gallos de Paris - Audiovisual material, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Javier Galván, 2009-2014, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Miguel Galvan, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Ralph Galvan Orchestra, 2009, 2011, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Tony Gamboa, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Andy Gamon, 1983-2001, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Andy Gamon - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Gananzia, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Los Garcia Bros. - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Los Garcia Bros., 1999, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Los Garcia Bros. - Publicity, 2000-2001, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Los Garcia Bros. - Clippings, 2001-2015, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Los Garcia Bros. - Audiovisual material, 2011-2014, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Abel Garcia, 1991, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Arthur Garcia, 2008, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Cristobal Garcia, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Cruz Garcia and the Latin Glows, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Dale Garcia, 1996, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Dan Garcia, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - David Garcia, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Delmiro Garcia - Personal, 1989, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Delmiro Garcia - Photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Delmiro Garcia - Business records and press releases, 1988-1990, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Delmiro Garcia - Ramón Hernández material, 1986-1990, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Delmiro Garcia - Clippings, 1989-2018, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Eddie Garcia, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Enrique "King" Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Felix Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Flaco Garcia y Los Andariegos de Houston, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Florinda Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Gilbert Garcia, 2015, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Jay Garcia and the Crusader Band, 1986, 2014, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Jerry Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Joe Garcia y Los Amigos, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Jose Luis Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Juan Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Larry Garcia y Grupo Experencia, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Manny "El Picante" Garcia, Jr., 2007-2013, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Martin Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Mingo Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Nat Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Ramón Garcia, 2011-2012 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - René Garcia, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Richard Garcia, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Shaggy Garcia y Grupo Recuerdo, 2012, 2014, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Ernie Garibay, 2006-2013, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Ernie Garibay - Clippings, 2006-2018, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Randy Garibay - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Randy Garibay - Concert and event publicity, 1992-2013, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Randy Garibay - Publicity, 1988, 2001, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Randy Garibay - Ramón Hernández material, 1986, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Randy Garibay - Clippings, 1986-2018, undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Los Garrapatas, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Gary and the Epics, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Gary the Showman, 2014-2015, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Bo Garza & Youngblood, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Bugz Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Cecilio Garza, 2012, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Chuy Garza and Los Inquietos, 1997, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Daniel Garza, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - David Garza, 1992, 1995, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - David Lee Garza - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - David Lee Garza - Publicity photographs, 1998, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - David Lee Garza - Personal, 1995, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - David Lee Garza - Concerts, 2009, 2011, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - David Lee Garza - Albums, 1988-2000, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - David Lee Garza - Publicity, [1985]-2002, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - David Lee Garza - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-1995, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - David Lee Garza - Clippings, 1986-2014, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - David Lee Garza - Clippings, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - David Lee Garza - Magazines, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - David Lee Garza - Magazine clippings, 2008, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - David Lee Garza - Promotional material, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Dimas Garza, 2008, 2018, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Donald Garza, 2006, 2016, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Edward Garza, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Fernando Garza, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Flavio Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Gus Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Humberto "Beto" Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Ignacio "Nacho" Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Javier Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Lee Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Leo Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Luz Garza, 2001, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Moses Garza y Los Hermanos Garza, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Pablo Garza, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Pete Garza, 2017, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Richard Garza, 2013, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Rick Garza y Raizz, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Santiago Garza y La Naturalez, 2017 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Wally Garza, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Daniel Garzes, 1954-2001, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Daniel Garzes - Events, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Daniel Garzes, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Daniel Garzes - Business correspondence and records, 1955-1986, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Daniel Garzes - Ramón Hernández material, 1986, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Daniel Garzes - Clippings, 1988-2008, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Los Gatos, 1996-2003, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Marcelo Gauna, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Gavino, 1995-1996, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Juan Gaytan - Personal, 1944, 1983, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Juan Gaytan - Correspondence, 1965-1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Juan Gaytan - Musical scores and lyrics (1 of 4), 1950-1970, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Juan Gaytan - Musical scores and lyrics (2 of 4), 1947-1974, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Juan Gaytan - Musical scores and lyrics (3 of 4), 1922-1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Juan Gaytan - Musical scores and lyrics (4 of 4), 1936-1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Juan Gaytan - Untitled scores and lyrics, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Juan Gaytan - Published sheet music, 1946, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Juan Gaytan - Notebooks, undated (Box 26, Folder 24-29, Box 27, Folder 1-7)
    - Juan Gaytan - Gaytan's original folders, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Juan Gaytan - Clippings, 1975, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Juan Gaytan - Framed portrait, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Gema, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - George and the Twilighters, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Gerado, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Los Gilitos, 1999, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Los Gilitos - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Gingbreadmen, 1991, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Al Gomez, 1991-2017, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ed Gomez, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Frank Gomez, 2010, 2012, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Frank Gomez - Audiovisual material, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Freddy Gomez, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Henry Gomez, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Jessie Gomez, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - JR Gomez, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Robert Gomez, 2000, 2013, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Ben Gonzales, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Ben Gonzales, 1989, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Hugo Gonzales y Su Conjunto, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Johnny Gonzales, 1989, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Johnny Gonzales - Clippings, 1971-2010, undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Juan Gonzales, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Leonardo Gonzales y Los Magnificos, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Louis Ayala Gonzales, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 23)